howtosavemoney.ca 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy | HowToSaveMoney.ca

Everything you're about to read below is just the long way of saying we care about your privacy and we won't share your personal information with anyone without your consent. Any personal information you give us, like your email address, will only be used to keep in touch with you or to carry out the exact thing you gave it us for, like participating in a contest for instance.

This site does generate some financial income and occasional other perks through advertising and by recommending products we believe in. However, only an extremely small percentage of our content generates any income whatsoever, except through clearly marked ads you will see on the page, like Google Adsense. We always give our honest opinion of any product we are discussing regardless if there is money involved or not.

All information you read on this site is our opinion only. We do our best to ensure it is factual but mistakes are made and information does become stale over time. We are not financial professionals and suggest you consult a professional before making any decisions that could impact you financially.

##  1\. Do we use cookies?

Yes, cookies are the small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

##  2\. Third party sites

We may include or offer third party products and services or ads on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites if you choose to engage with them.

##  3\. Google as a third party site

Google, as a third party site, uses the DART cookie to serve ads to you on our site and many other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Please visit the links below for information about Google privacy policies.

<http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>  
<http://www.google.com/privacy.html>

##  4\. Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

##  5\. Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or send an email notifying you of any changes.

##  6\. Disclaimer

All content provided on this website is for informational purposes only. The owner of this blog makes no representations as to the accuracy or completeness of any information on this site or found by following any link on this site. This website accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation. The compensation received will never influence the content, topics or posts made on this website.

The views and opinions expressed on this website are purely the owner’s or those of the author of the content. If we claim or appear to be experts on a certain topic, product, or service, we will only endorse those products or services that we believe, based on our expertise, are worthy of such endorsement. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer or provider.

##  7\. Feedback

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using our [contact form](http://www.howtosavemoney.ca/contact).
